var javaScript = [
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript data type?",
        "answer": "True",
        "choice1": "Number",
        "choice2": "String",
        "choice3": "Boolean",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript variable declaration?",
        "answer": "div",
        "choice1": "var",
        "choice2": "let",
        "choice3": "const",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript variable declaration has a global scope?",
        "answer": "var",
        "choice1": "let",
        "choice2": "const",
        "choice3": "function",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript variable declarations has a block scope?",
        "answer": "let",
        "choice1": "var",
        "choice2": "function",
        "choice3": "num",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an increment operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "++",
        "choice1": "--",
        "choice2": "//",
        "choice3": "&&",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a single line comment in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "//",
        "choice1": "<!--",
        "choice2": "#",
        "choice3": "%",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": '"\xa0\xa0"',
        "choice1": "&&",
        "choice2": "||",
        "choice3": "!",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the AND logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "&&",
        "choice1": "||",
        "choice2": "!",
        "choice3": '"\xa0\xa0"',
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the OR logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "||",
        "choice1": "&&",
        "choice2": "!",
        "choice3": '"\xa0\xa0"',
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the NOT logical operator in JavaScript?",
        "answer": "!",
        "choice1": "&&",
        "choice2": "||",
        "choice3": '"\xa0\xa0"',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a correctly defined JavaScript function?",
        "answer": "function myFunction()",
        "choice1": "function myFunction[]",
        "choice2": "function myFunction{}",
        "choice3": "function == myFunction()",
    },
    {
        "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the script?",
        "answer": "<script>",
        "choice1": "<js>",
        "choice2": "<javascript>",
        "choice3": "<body>",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for linking an external JavaScript file?",
        "answer": '<script src="xxx.js">',
        "choice1": '<script href="xxx.js">',
        "choice2": '<script alt="xxx.js">',
        "choice3": 'getElement("xxx.js")',
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you call a function named myFunction?",
        "answer": "myFunction()",
        "choice1": "call myFunction()",
        "choice2": "alert(myFunction)",
        "choice3": "getElement(myFunction)",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the index number of the first element in a JavaScript array?",
        "answer": "0",
        "choice1": "1",
        "choice2": "2",
        "choice3": "3",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a correct JavaScript array?",
        "answer": 'var classmates = ["Bob","Jane","Mary"]',
        "choice1": 'var classmates = {"Bob","Jane","Mary"}',
        "choice2": 'var classmates = ("Bob","Jane","Mary")',
        "choice3": 'var classmates = [1:"Bob",2:"Jane",3:"Mary"]',
    }, 
    {
        "question": "How do you return the number of elements in a JavaScript array?",
        "answer": "array.length",
        "choice1": "array.numberElements",
        "choice2": "array.getLength",
        "choice3": "array(totalElements)",
    }
]

var python = [
    {
        "question": "How do you allow a user to enter a value that is stored as a string in Python?",
        "answer": 'input("Enter a value: ")',
        "choice1": 'cin("Enter a value: ")',
        "choice2": 'insert("Enter a value: ")',
        "choice3": 'prompt("Enter a value: ")',
    },
    {
        "question": 'How do you output "Hello World" to the user in Python?',
        "answer": 'print("Hello World")',
        "choice1": 'output("Hello World")',
        "choice2": 'display("Hello World")',
        "choice3": 'cout("Hello World")',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Python reserved word?",
        "answer": "local",
        "choice1": "global",
        "choice2": "assert",
        "choice3": "yield",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you begin a single line comment in Python?",
        "answer": "#",
        "choice1": "<!--",
        "choice2": "//",
        "choice3": "%",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the modulo operator in Python?",
        "answer": "%",
        "choice1": "^",
        "choice2": "*",
        "choice3": "#",
    },
    {
        "question": 'How do you reverse the string "Hello World" in Python?',
        "answer": '"Hello World[::-1]"',
        "choice1": 'reverse("Hello World")',
        "choice2": '"Hello World".switch',
        "choice3": '"Hello World"(end 0)',
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct file etension for Python files?",
        "answer": ".py",
        "choice1": ".pyth",
        "choice2": ".pt",
        "choice3": ".js",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which operator is used to multiply numbers in Python?",
        "answer": "*",
        "choice1": "x",
        "choice2": "#",
        "choice3": "%",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a TUPLE in Python?",
        "answer": '("apple", "bananan", "cherry")',
        "choice1": '["apple", "bananan", "cherry"]',
        "choice2": '{"apple", "bananan", "cherry"}',
        "choice3": '/"apple", "bananan", "cherry"/',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a SET in Python?",
        "answer": '{"apple", "bananan", "cherry"}',
        "choice1": '["apple", "bananan", "cherry"]',
        "choice2": '("apple", "bananan", "cherry")',
        "choice3": '/"apple", "bananan", "cherry"/',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a LIST in Python?",
        "answer": '["apple", "bananan", "cherry"]',
        "choice1": '{"apple", "bananan", "cherry"}',
        "choice2": '("apple", "bananan", "cherry")',
        "choice3": '/"apple", "bananan", "cherry"/',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to define a DICTIONARY in Python?",
        "answer": '["name": "apple", "color": "red"]',
        "choice1": '{"apple", "bananan", "cherry"}',
        "choice2": '("apple", "bananan", "cherry")',
        "choice3": '/"apple", "bananan", "cherry"/',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is unordered and unindexed?",
        "answer": 'Set',
        "choice1": 'List',
        "choice2": 'Tuple',
        "choice3": 'Dictionary',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is ordered and unchangeable?",
        "answer": "Tuple",
        "choice1": "Set",
        "choice2": "List",
        "choice3": "Dictionary",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections is ordered and changeable?",
        "answer": "List",
        "choice1": "Set",
        "choice2": "Tuple",
        "choice3": "Dictionary",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Python collections stores data in key:value pairs?",
        "answer": "Dictionary",
        "choice1": "Set",
        "choice2": "Tuple",
        "choice3": "List",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the index number of the first element in a Python array?",
        "answer": "0",
        "choice1": "1",
        "choice2": "2",
        "choice3": "3",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing an if statement in Python?",
        "answer": "if x > y:",
        "choice1": "if x > y then:",
        "choice2": "if (x > y)",
        "choice3": "if => x > y",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing a while loop in Python?",
        "answer": "while x > y:",
        "choice1": "while (x > y)",
        "choice2": "while x > y {",
        "choice3": "while => x > y",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you start writing a for loop in Python?",
        "answer": "for x in y:",
        "choice1": "for x > y",
        "choice2": "for each x in y",
        "choice3": "for (x > y)",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statemen is used to stop a loop in Python?",
        "answer": "break",
        "choice1": "return",
        "choice2": "stop",
        "choice3": "exit",
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you return the number of elements in a Python list?",
        "answer": "len(listName)",
        "choice1": "listName.numberElements",
        "choice2": "listName.length",
        "choice3": "listName(totalElements)",
    }
]

var cPlusPlus = [
    {
        "question": 'How do you output "Hello World!" in C++?',
        "answer": 'cout >> "Hellow World!";',
        "choice1": 'print("Hello World!")',
        "choice2": 'prompt("Hello World!")',
        "choice3": 'output("Hello World!")',
    },
    {
        "question": "How do single line comments begin in C++?",
        "answer": '//',
        "choice1": '##',
        "choice2": '%',
        "choice3": '</',
    },
    {
        "question": "How do multi-line comments begin in C++?",
        "answer": '/*',
        "choice1": '##',
        "choice2": '%',
        "choice3": '<<',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a variable type in C++?",
        "answer": 'varchar',
        "choice1": 'bool',
        "choice2": 'float',
        "choice3": 'void',
    },
    {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": 'answer',
        "choice1": '1',
        "choice2": 'float',
        "choice3": 'void',
    },
]